gantthead.com 2008-12-20

# gantthead.com Privacy Policy

Home  >  gantthead.com Privacy Policy 

_**gantthead.com**_

_**PRIVACY POLICY**_

**_Why a Privacy Policy?_**

The gantthead.com privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") recognizes that you need appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information that you share with us, including any information that identifies you personally, such as name, address and telephone number. 

We have established this privacy policy so you can understand how carefully we intend to treat the information you provide to [www.gantthead.com](http://www.gantthead.com/) (the "Web Site"). 

**_What information does gantthead.com collect?_**

We gather certain personal information about you, including your: 

  * name
  * address
  * e-mail address and
  * company information

Certain portions of the Web Site may prompt you to provide other personal information in your user profile, may ask you to answer demographic or personal preference questions, or may ask for financial information to complete a purchase. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you do so, you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services on the Web Site. 

We also track the Internet address of the domains from which users visit us and information about which advertisements are displayed to a user, which advertisements a user clicked on and a subscriber's other interactions with the Web Site. gantthead.com also tracks subscribers' traffic patterns throughout their online sessions, including which web sites a subscriber visits while using the Web Site and which pages a subscriber views while using the Web Site. 

**_How We Gather Information_**

_Forms_

When you register with gantthead.com, the registration form requires you to give us certain personal information about you. We also gather information through other forms or questions that you may answer on the Web Site. 

_Cookies_

Some of the pages on the Web Site utilize cookies so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers that a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to accept or reject it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and to provide us with the technical information for the personalization that lets us tailor our site to your preferences. 

_Other_

We use software to track the Internet address of the domains from which users visit us. 

**_How We Use Information_**

Information we obtain from you is used to: 

  * provide and/or improve our level and scope of service to you, including by providing additional newsletters or mailings from us or our affiliates that may be of interest to you.
  * fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as newsletters.
  * analyze trends and statistics.
  * diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site.
  * gather and analyze demographic and marketing information.
  * allow gantthead.com to send you updates and other information regarding the Web Site.
  * allow gantthead.com to send you promotional information that may be of interest to you.
  * with your consent, to allow third parties to send you promotional information that may be of interest to you.

**_With Whom Do We Share Your Information?_**

_Personally Identifiable Information_

We may make your personally identifiable information available to third parties when: 

  * we have your consent to share the information.
  * they provide services or products on behalf of gantthead.com; provided that they do not have the right to use your information for any purpose other than to provide the applicable service.
  * you use co-branded services.
  * they are affiliates subject to privacy policies that protect your personally identifiable information from disclosure to third parties in a manner similar to this Privacy Policy.
  * we sell, assign or transfer a part of our business that provides a particular service to you; provided, that your personally identifiable information may be sold, assigned or transferred only to the acquirer as a part of such transaction.
  * we are required to do so by law, regulation, rule or court order; pursuant to requests from governmental agencies or law enforcement authorities.
  * necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our User Agreement.
  * necessary to protect gantthead.com, our members or other third parties including, without limitation, other emergency situations.

If you wish to opt out of any service from gantthead.com or to revoke any previously provided consent, please send an e-mail to us with such instructions at contactus@gantthead.com. 

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

Without your consent, gantthead.com may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other parties for marketing, promotional and other purposes. Except as set forth above, we do not disclose without your consent any information that could be used to identify you personally. 

**_How to Update Information_**

You may update information previously provided to gantthead.com, including any consents provided to or withheld from gantthead.com, by sending an email to [contactus@gantthead.com](mailto:contactus@gantthead.com). 

**_Security of Information_**

The Web Site has certain security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although no security measure is foolproof, we believe that we have implemented a system that is as safe as today's technology permits. Our network firewall is a combination of hardware and software designed to keep unauthorized users from accessing our network. Any potentially sensitive data, including credit card payment information, is encrypted prior to transmission.

**_Third Party Advertisers_**

Third parties may display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web Site, cookies received with banner ads may be collected by ad companies, and we may not have access to this information or be able to control its distribution. 

**_Discussion Forums_**

The Web Site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available for you to use. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**_Links to Other Sites_**

The Web Site may contain links to other sites. gantthead.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, notwithstanding the inclusion on such sites of the trademarks of gantthead.com. 

**_This Policy Subject to Change_**

We may modify this privacy policy from time to time. Our current privacy policy will be published on our Web Site. If you have any questions, or if you do not understand any provision of this privacy policy, e-mail [contactus@gantthead.com](mailto:contactus@gantthead.com).

**_Legal Agreement_**

This Privacy Policy forms a legal agreement between you and gantthead.com. Your use of the Web Site indicates your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. You agree that the Electronic Communications Privacy Act (the "ECPA") shall not apply to any communications with gantthead.com. gantthead.com has the right to revise this Agreement at any time without notice by updating the Privacy Policy posted to the Web Site. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Web Site or your dealings with this Web Site, please contact [contactus@gantthead.com](mailto:contactus@gantthead.com). 

gantthead.com, Inc.  
4035 Ridge Top Rd.  
Suite 300  
Fairfax, VA, 22030  
(800) 895-2535  
E-mail: [contactus@gantthead.com](mailto:contactus@gantthead.com). 

Thank you for your support of gantthead.com and its Privacy Policy. 

Last updated July 11, 2005. 

sponsored announcements and special offers

**["Selecting the Right Requirements Management Tool – Or Maybe None Whatsoever"](http://www.gantthead.com/redirect/clickCount.cfm?ID=245032)** – Get your **free copy** of this independent report by Forrester Research, compliments of MKS. 

**Since incomplete, inaccurate, and misunderstood requirements are a major source of project failures, identifying the "right" requirements for initiatives has become a high-stakes activity.** **[Learn about IBM Rational Requirements Definition and Management solutions and best practices.](http://www.gantthead.com/redirect/clickCount.cfm?ID=246093)**

**Coming Soon: _New Editions_ of Four PMI Standards. Pre-order Yours Now!** Special combo offer: Pre-order one standard, get a second standard 40% off! Start meeting your standards for better project performance. Order today at **[PMI.org/MyStandards](http://www.gantthead.com/redirect/clickCount.cfm?ID=246241)**

**There is a balance between monitoring and blocking web use in the workplace.** IT Managers need to determine the best way to deal with employee internet access while keeping the overall good of the business a priority. **[Download this whitepaper](http://www.gantthead.com/redirect/clickCount.cfm?ID=246371)** to help make an informed decision about your own web monitoring requirements 

**PPM WEBCAST: How Misys PLC Improved Global Resource Management — Hosted by CA**  
Join us for this live webcast as Misys PLC discusses how they improved global visibility into their projects and portfolios while streamlining the allocation of resources across the enterprise using CA Clarity™ PPM. This interactive webcast will include a live Q&A session. **[Register now.](http://www.gantthead.com/redirect/clickCount.cfm?ID=246295)**
